thinksimplenow.com 2012-06-03

# Privacy Policy | Think Simple Now

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or email address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for our information about cookies and how we use them.

### ****

### **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service. Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering purchased product or service requested.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you may.

### How do we protect customer information?

We use a Secure Server for collecting personal and credit card information. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts (scrambles) all of the information you enter before it is transmitted over the interenet and sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.  

### ****

### **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity or our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the [California Online Privacy Protection Act](http://www.oispp.ca.gov/consumer_privacy/default.asp). We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### **Change to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Popular search terms for this article:

[simple privacy policy](http://thinksimplenow.com/privacy/ "simple privacy policy"), [sample simple privacy policy](http://thinksimplenow.com/privacy/ "sample simple privacy policy"), [simple private policy example](http://thinksimplenow.com/privacy/ "simple private policy example"), [Susan Jeffers African Mango](http://thinksimplenow.com/privacy/ "Susan Jeffers African Mango"), [think simple now unsubscribe](http://thinksimplenow.com/privacy/ "think simple now unsubscribe"), [thinksimply website](http://thinksimplenow.com/privacy/ "thinksimply website"), [how to unsubscribe think simple now from facebook](http://thinksimplenow.com/privacy/ "how to unsubscribe think simple now from facebook"), [to process transactions privacy sample simple](http://thinksimplenow.com/privacy/ "to process transactions privacy sample simple"), [unsubscribe](http://thinksimplenow.com/privacy/ "unsubscribe"), [We collect information from you when you place an order subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey](http://thinksimplenow.com/privacy/ "We collect information from you when you place an order subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey")
